seesaw.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  

"SeeSaw" is a television service made available on the internet at [www.seesaw.com](http://www.seesaw.com/) which allows you to access and view content on SeeSaw in accordance with our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.seesaw.com/TermsAndConditions). SeeSaw is provided by SeeSaw IPTV Limited, a limited company registered in England and Wales with registered number 7140424, VAT registration number 987 5773 41 and whose registered office is Crawley Court, Winchester, Hampshire, SO21 2QA (" **we** " or " **us** "). 

This privacy policy describes how we collect, use and look after the information you provide us with when you use SeeSaw and any information you provide us with when you take part in any promotions (such as competitions, prize draws or giveaways) that are run by us whether on SeeSaw or otherwise (“ **SeeSaw Promotion** ”). We are committed to protecting your privacy and we take our responsibilities regarding the security of your personal data very seriously. We collect and process personal data only in compliance with applicable Data Protection legislation.

**What information we collect**

This is the information that we would normally collect about you when you use SeeSaw and/or take part in any SeeSaw Promotion: 

  * Any personal information about you (such as your name, address, date of birth, email address and purchase history) which you give us if you choose to register on the SeeSaw website or to purchase Rental Content and/or Subscription Content or if you choose to take part in any SeeSaw Promotion (see our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.seesaw.com/TermsAndConditions) for the definition of “Rental Content” and “Subscription Content”). 
  * Any information which you provide to us by email or otherwise through or in connection with SeeSaw (e.g. if you provide your email address, name, address or other information when you contact us or participate in research or a survey with us). 
  * Your IP address (this is a number which is assigned to the device you use to access the internet). 
  * We will use cookies to collect information about how you use SeeSaw (see below for more information about cookies). 

**How we use your information**  

We will use your information to administer and monitor your use of SeeSaw and/or participation in any SeeSaw Promotion, respond to and keep track of your purchases and enquiries and improve the quality of SeeSaw and our services. We will also use your information to contact you with regard to your use of SeeSaw such as with updates on your purchases, service disruption messages and alerts and payment confirmation and in relation to your participation in any SeeSaw Promotion. From time to time, so long as you are aged 16 years or over and have consented to us contacting you, we may use your information to send you details of services, special offers, promotions and other information in relation to SeeSaw and/or any SeeSaw Promotion. In addition, from time to time we may use your information to report to our third party content suppliers and/or to conduct market research and analysis, including statistical analysis of user behaviour, which we may disclose to third parties, in each case, in de-personalised aggregated form. 

Unless there is a specific legal requirement to keep your personal information we will not keep it for longer than necessary for the purposes for which the personal information was collected or for which it is to be further processed. 

**Updating your information**  

You may update, amend or correct your personal information which you have provided on the SeeSaw website by editing your personal details in the ‘My Account’ section in your ‘Latch’ on SeeSaw. You may delete your personal information by closing your account on SeeSaw (through ‘Cancel My Account’ in the settings menu in the ‘My Account’ section in your ‘Latch’) although your personal information will remain on our databases for as long as is necessary in accordance with the paragraph above. 

**Enquiries**  

You may have rights of access to and correction of any personal data that we hold about you under data protection law. If you wish to exercise those rights or have queries about this privacy policy you can send an email to [info@seesaw.com](mailto:info@seesaw.com). If you do request us to provide you with any information we may have about you then we will need to charge you £10 to cover our administration costs. 

**Disclosure to third parties**  

We never disclose your personal data to any other person or organisation without your consent unless we have said so in this privacy policy or there is an emergency situation that requires it or we are legally required to do so. 

We may pass your personal data on to other companies which are affiliated or associated with SeeSaw IPTV Limited to enable us to process your personal data for the purposes identified in this privacy policy. 

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include providing website administration and development services, conducting customer research and satisfaction surveys, processing credit card payments and providing customer services. These third parties will have access to such personal information as they need to perform their functions for us but they may not use it for other purposes. These third parties may be located outside the European Economic Area which may require us to transfer data a country outside the European Economic Area which does not have laws or regulations to protect personal data which are equivalent to those in the UK. However, in such cases we will ensure that such third parties enter into appropriate contractual commitments with respect to their protection and processing of such data. 

We may provide aggregated statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-parties, but these statistics will not include any personal data. 

**Security to protect your information**  

As required by the UK Data Protection Act 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us to prevent unauthorised access. Any personal information you provide to us through your use of the SeeSaw website and/or participation in SeeSaw Promotions will be protected using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. This is industry standard encryption technology that protects your data whilst being sent over the internet from being intercepted and misused by third parties. When it reaches us, we then store it on a secure server so that it can only be accessed by authorised personnel. Where you are paying for Rental Content and/or Subscription Content, your payments will be processed by an independent third party who we have appointed as our payment service provider and who are a Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) level one compliant payment service provider. Our payment service provider will not disclose your credit card or debit card details to us at any time except that they will give us the last four (4) digits of the long number of your credit card or debit card when they confirm that you have paid for any Rental Content and/or Subscription Content. 

Please be aware that although we make every effort to create a secure environment for your personal information, because transmission of data via the internet is never completely secure, we cannot guarantee the safety of any personal information you transmit to us online. In addition, where you need a password to use SeeSaw, it is important that you keep your password secure and confidential and protect against unauthorised access to and use of your password. 

**Cookies**  

You should be aware that by using SeeSaw and/or participate in any SeeSaw Promotion, information and data may be automatically collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive and enable us to provide or improve the features of SeeSaw and/or SeeSaw Promotions. Like most website providers, we use cookies to enable us to make a link between you and the information you have provided on the SeeSaw website and therefore to personalise your use of SeeSaw so that we can give you a better experience when you return and provide features such as recommendations and ‘keep me signed in’ functionality. Cookies can be deleted from your hard drive if you wish. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser settings to prevent that. If you disable cookies, you will not be able to access the SeeSaw website. For further information about managing and disabling cookies, you can refer to your browser’s help section or user guide. Alternatively, the Interactive Advertising Bureau has produced a series of web pages (see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)) which explain to users how cookies work and can be managed. More information about cookies can also be found in the [Help area](http://www.seesaw.com/Help) on our website. 

**Site tracking**  

We use tracking software to monitor customer traffic patterns and website usage to help us develop the design and layout of SeeSaw to better meet the needs of visitors to seesaw.com and to enhance your use of SeeSaw including, for example, providing recommendations or other facilities as they become available. 

**Advertising and Third Party Sites**  

SeeSaw includes third party advertising. We do not provide any personal data to these advertisers. However, these third party advertisers may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to track the number of users viewing and/or responding to the ad. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use and the privacy practices of these third party advertisers are not covered by this privacy policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. 

We may provide links or pointers to third party websites and/or make SeeSaw Promotions available on third party websites not under our control. If you follow a link to any of these websites and /or take part in a SeeSaw Promotion on a third party websites, please note that they have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites to understand how personal information that is collected about you is used and protected. 

We may use behavioural targeting technology to swap out standard advertisements and promotions for ones which are likely to be more relevant to you. For behavioural advertising we may use the personal information which you have given to us together with your use of the SeeSaw website to deliver advertisements to you which are more relevant to you and tailored to your interests. Where we use a third party to provide this behavioural advertising, then we will only provide anonymous information to such third party which enables audience segmentation and appropriate targeting of such behavioural advertising. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy  **

Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to time. If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and in what circumstances we disclose it. You should check this privacy policy frequently to see recent changes. Your use of the SeeSaw website and/or participation in any SeeSaw Promotion will be subject to the privacy policy on the SeeSaw website at the time of each use. 

**Version 4    
Published: November 2010**
